What can I do with it? I'm going to stay
with her. I'm going to stay with her.
I'm going I'm going I'm going I'm going
I'm going I'm going you about to be so
fire insurance common.
Marine insurance increase of in the
other
number in Kansas
and the number one
first government will be in the number
of the number one partner so in the
Mariana in Mariana insurance opportunity
to opportunity in the
number one number in the number one
partner
If you
listen to first analyze the result in
the number one
analyze the revenue 1.29% year on year
increase and the number one net profit
1.15% year on year increase in the
number
If you want to
EPS in the number one so EPS growth rate
cash EPS on year growth rate number one
in the number
one number one number one number one
number one number one number one number
one number one number one
one number one number one number one
number one number one number one number
number one number one quarterly revenue
1.22% year on year increase and the
number one quarterly net profit 1.22%
year on year increase
and the number one number one number one
number one number one number one number
one number one number one number one
number one number one number one
miscellaneous number one number one
number one number one number one number
one number one number one number one
one number one number one
number one number one number one number
one number one number one number one
number one number one
number one number one number one number
one number one number one number one
profit
profit contributions with the in the
comparison in the either one
contributions if you want to be
quarterly number one of quarterly or EPS
in the novel quarterly love in the novel
quarterly
number one
in the number 28 of in the range of in
the range number 21 with the number 21
with the number 21 with the number 21
number 21 with the number 21 with the
number 21 number 21 with the number 21
with the number 21 with the number 21
number 21 with the number 21 number 21
number 21 with the number 21 with the
number number 21 with the number 21 with
the number 21 number 21 with number 21
with the number 21 with the number 21
with the number 21 number 21 with the
number 21 number 21 with the number 21
with the number 21 with the
number 21 with the number 21 with the
number 21 with number 21 with the number
21 with the number 21 with number 21
with the
number 21 with the number 21 with the
number 21 number 21 with the number 21
with the number 21 number 21 with the
number 21 with the number 21 number 21
with the number 21 with the number 21
number 21 with the number 21 with the
number 21 with the number 21
with number 21 with the number 21 number
21 with the number 21 with the number 21
with
number 21 with the number 21 with the
number 21 number 21 with the number 21
with the number 21
number 21 with the number 21 with the
number 21
number 21 number 21 with the number 21
with the number 21 with the number 21
number 21 with the number 21 with the
number 21
with number 21 with the number 21 with
the number 21
number 21 with the number
number 21 with the number 21 with the
number number 21 with the number number
21 with number 21 with the number 21
with the number 21 number 21 with the
number 21 with the number
number 21 with the number 21 with the
number 21 loss
damage
premium premium collect
loss
maintain
statistics
claim
standardize maintain
main which is a
investment
aspect
adequate liquidity position
manageable
company
equity
zero
expensive valuation
industry median
expensive valuation affordability
willing to purchase
the financial sources
professionals
institutions
expensive valuation
performance stagnant out of decrease
correction
net cash positive
relative
percent
beta score
normal volatility
next quarter quarter going to wipe in
the bathroom.
I'm going to put it on the road.
If I had next quarter going to average
estimation number 4 to move 13.53 in
order.
It every number calculate of this one
like that.
If you sort of current EPS or the TTM
other than the next quarter exit out of
order to college to balance more than
average number of this one like that
next quarter going to average estimated
EPS or that is 13.53 in order to pay the
13 in order to next quarter exit out of
order to
other than the one coming out of order
EPS or the 54 out of order to for you
wipe out of order to average estimation
order to pay the one order to upside
movement out of support out of order to
upside movement out of order. I don't
want to number of the average estimation
number of the
other than the one out of order to wipe
out of order to average estimation order
to pay the one
order to upside movement out of support
out of order to upside movement out of
order to average estimation order to pay
the one
order to upside movement out of support
out of order to upside movement out of
order to average estimation order to pay
the one order to upside movement out of
support out of order to upside movement
out of order to average estimation order
to pay the one order to upside movement
out of support out of order to upside
movement out of order to average
estimation order to pay the one order to
upside movement out of support out of
order to upside movement out of order to
average estimation order to pay the one
order to upside movement out of support
out of order to upside movement I don't
want to number of the average estimation
number of the other than the one out of
order to wipe out of order to average
estimation order to pay the one order to
upside movement out of support out of
order to upside movement out of order to
average estimation order to pay the one
order to upside movement out of support
out of order to upside movement out of
order to average estimation order to pay
the one order to upside movement out of
support out of order to upside movement
out of order to average estimation order
to pay the one order to upside movement
out of support out of order to upside
movement out of order to average
estimation order to pay the one order to
upside movement out of support out of
order to upside movement out of order to
average estimation order to pay the one
order to upside movement out of support
out of order to upside movement out of
order to average estimation order to pay
the one order to upside movement out of
support out of order to upside movement
out of order to average estimation order
to pay the one order to upside movement
out of support out of order to upside
movement out of order to average
estimation order to pay
Correct out. you know they bought top
level in the support road zone of the
top level
support and mid point in the ground up
in the end of our s1 1565
s2 s1 mid point 1371
s2 1194
If you want to already bought the money
s1 top even support it to mail you up
mail upon mid point in the 1800 mid
point in the s1 r1 another mid point
other break mail you
if you mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the
mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up in the mail up in
the mail up in the mail up in the mail
up in the mail up in the mail up in the
mail up in the mail up
direction leader
Suppose yes.
the support
the structure
It would have me
midpoint
Yes, too.
the quarterly maximum on the resistance
R1
or strong resistance
annualized
midpoint
R2
So people
If I analyze
video
important
R1
R2
update R3
over 100
update
The double
number
Shaka Samsung